Guide to the Stan Steiner Papers, ca. 1940-1987 M0700
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series XII. Steiner Library
  - Malinowski, Bronislaw, 1884-1942. Magic, science and religion, and other essays. With an introduction by Robert Redfield. Garden City, N.Y., Doubleday, 1954 [c1948]. Reprint. Originally published: Glencoe, Ill.: Free Press, 1948. 274 p. 18 cm. (Doubleday anchor books, A23)
    Note: p. 100 marked "Myth and reality" First four lines of second full paragraph underlined; p. 107 marked "Folktales, legends, and myths" Last five lines of first full paragraph underscored; p. 110 marked "Death and Myth" Eighth line of page marked with word "Death" circled; p. 146 marked "Myth and culture" lines 17 to 27 marked. First line of first full paragraph "Myth is, therefore, an indispensible ingredient of all culture" underscored.
  - Mann, Thomas, 1875-1955. Confessions of Felix Krull, confidence man. Tr. from the German by Denver Lindley. New York: Signet Books, 1957. 319 p. Translation of Bekenntnisse des Hochstaplers Felix Krull; der Memoiren erster Teil.
  - Maule, Harry E. (Harry Edward), 1886 -. Great tales of the American West, edited, and with an introduction by Harry E. Maule. New York, The Modern Library [1945]. xviii, 361 p. 19 cm. (The Modern library of the world's best books)
  - Melville, Herman, 1819-1891. Moby Dick: or, The white whale / by Herman Melville; with an afterword by Denham Sutcliffe. New York: New American Library, 1961 (Signet Classics) 543 p.
  - Neil, J. Meredith, 1937-. Toward a national taste: America's quest for aesthetic independence. Honolulu, University Press of Hawaii [1975]. xiii,402 p. 23cm. Bibliography: p. [359]-389.
  - Romanov's Russian-English, English-Russian dictionary, with special emphasis on American English. Part I by E. Wedel. Part II by A. Romanov. [1st American ed.] New York, Washington Square Press, Inc. [1964]. 505 p. 19 cm. (A Langenscheidt dictionary [L-32]). Issued also under title: Langenscheidt's Russian-English, English Russian dictionary.
  - Santayana, George, 1863-1952. Reason in common sense / George Santayana. New York: Dover Publications, 1980. ix, 291 p.; 20 cm. (His The life of reason; v. 1) Notes: "An unabridged republication of volume one of The life of reason; or The phases of human progress, originally published by Charles Scribner's Sons in 1905."
  - The Goliard poets; medieval Latin songs and satires with verse translation by George F. Whicher. [Norfolk, Conn., New Directions, 1949]. 303 p. illus. 24 cm.
  - Thomas, D. M. Ararat / D.M. Thomas. New York: Pocket Books, 1983. 191 p.; 23 cm.
  - Thomas, Dylan, 1914-1953. Portrait of the artist as a young dog / by Dylan Thomas. New York: New Directions, c1940. 160 p.; 18 cm. (New Directions paperbook)
  - unidentified volume in Russian
  - Wessely, J. E. (Ignaz Emanuel), 1841-1900. Junior classic Italian dictionary. Italian-English, English-Italian, with supplement of Italian geographical, historical, and mythological, proper names, by J.E. Wessely. Rev. and enl. by O. Durante. Chicago, Follett publishing company, 1943. 200, 226 p. 18 cm. The junior classics series
  - Wolff, Hans Julius, 1902-. Roman law: an historical introduction / by Hans Julius Wolff. Norman: University of Oklahoma Press, 1951, 1982 printing. 260 p.; 22 cm. Notes: Includes index. Bibliography: p. 226-237.
  - Wright, Richard, 1908-1960. Uncle Tom's children: five long stories. Cleveland; New York: World Pub. Co., c1938 [1943]. 250 p.; 21 cm.